

Ismail Suleimanov Software Engineer

+90 530 570 2428

ismailmslmnv@gmail.com

★ ismailslmnv.github.io

Sakarya, Turkey

SUMMARY

I am an exited and open to learn developer and junior entrepreneur from Sakarya. I have worked in many projects during collage and early work life. I could define myself as agile, chatty, curious, thoughtful, researcher and bookworm.

EXPERIENCE

Development Team Leader - Scrum Master

Softinyo Bilişim ve Güvenlik Teknolojileri

Planning and managing projects, taking responsibilities to clients, making pricing and timing of each project, exploring new technologies to use

Server Side Developer 01/2020 - 08/2020

Softinyo Bilişim ve Güvenlik Teknolojileri

Development of Server Side Applications and API using Python programming language

Mobile Developer 01/2020 - 08/2020

Softinyo Bilişim ve Güvenlik Teknolojileri

Development of various mobile projects using different programming languages:

Java, C# Xamarin, Flutter/Dart

Co-founder and Communication Software Developer

Project T4H

Development of Mavlink applications for UAV.

Experience gained on:

PyMavlink,

Dronekit,

Gazebo STL

Project Consultant And Manager

03/2019 - 08/2019

02/2019 - Present

08/2020 - Present

4M Teknoloji

Managing, Planning and Consulting the Curriculum of Robotics projects for High School level students.

Educator 01/2018 - 07/2018

4M Teknoloji

Educating basics of electronics and algorithms to 5-15 years old kids.

- · Basic sensor and electronics
- C/C++ Coding
- Arduino

Technical Support Specialist

10/ - 01/2018

4M Teknoloji

Technical Support on IT devices (PC, Network, 3D Printers)

EDUCATION

Information Systems Engineering

Sakarya University - Bachelor's Degree

• Founding and Managing very first UAV community and team of the university.

CERTIFICATES

Kubernetes in the Google Cloud

01/2018 - Present

SKILLS

Python	Advanced	Java	Intermediate
C#	Expert	Flutter	Intermediate
SQL	Expert	Xamarin	Advanced
PHP	Intermediate	Arduino	Advanced
C++	Intermediate	Sensors And Electronics	Advanced

LANGUAGES

English	Fluent	Turkish	Native
Georgian	Intermediate	Azerbaijani	Native
Russian	Basic	Polish	Basic

2021